Parapsychology Laboratory Records, 1893-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research Files Series, 1912-1917and 1937-1963, 235 containers (117.5 lin. ft.)
  - Experimenter Files, 1912-1965
    - Davidson, W.
      - Rat PK experiments, 1945-1946 (Box 421)
      - Rat PK experiment 4, 1946-1948, (6 folders) (Box 421)
      - Rat PK experiment 4, 1946-1948, (10 folders) (Box 422)
    - Dean, D. New Jersey College for Women study, 1952 (Box 423)
    - Edris, J. High school group tests, 1947 (Box 423)
    - Ellis, L.
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1945-1946, (2 folders) (Box 423)
      - IQ and ESP, 1945-1946, (2 folders) (Box 423)
      - Psychokinesis trials, 1945-1946 (Box 423)
      - Student ESP trials, 1945 (Box 423)
      - Summary of date, 1945-1949 (Box 423)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1946-1947 (Box 423)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1946-1947 (Box 424)
      - High-low aim PK, 1947 (Box 424)
      - Psychokinesis group tests, 1947 (Box 424)
      - Pseudo-telepathy, 1947 (Box 424)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1947-1948, (5 folders) (Box 424)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1947-1948, (5 folders) (Box 425)
      - Group vs. alone DT, 1948-1949, (3 folders) (Box 425)
      - Group vs. alone DT, 1949 (Box 426)
      - PK–drawings, 1949, (6 folders) (Box 426)
      - Clairvoyant drawings, 1950 (Box 426)
      - Precognition runs, 1950 (Box 426)
      - Precognition-drawings, 1950 (Box 426)
      - Precognition-drawings, 1950 (Box 427)
      - Personality questionnnaires, 1950 (Box 427)
      - SMT trials, 1950 (Box 427)
      - Personality questionnaires, 1950-1951, (2 folders) (Box 427)
      - Clairvoyance–drawings, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 427)
      - DT scores, 1951 (Box 427)
      - Questionnaires and drawings, 1951 (Box 427)
      - Targets and drawings, 1951 (Box 427)
      - Targets and drawings, 1951 (Box 428)
      - Conviction series, 1951-1952, (7 folders) (Box 428)
    - Fahler, J.
      - ESP record sheets, 1955-1956 (Box 428)
      - ESP record sheets, 1956 (Box 428)
      - Hypnosis-waking study, 1957-1958, (18 folders) (Box 429)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 429)
    - Foster, E.
      - Analysis of L. Marchesi data, 1946-1947 (Box 429)
      - Prefontal lobotomy research, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 429)
      - Grouping of hits, 1955 (Box 430)
      - Cross checks, undated (Box 430)
      - Judge's criteria study, undated (Box 430)
    - Fraser, H. STM vs GSTM, 1936-1937 (Box 430)
    - George, R.W.
      - ESP in a life situation, 1938-1941, (2 folders) (Box 430)
      - Ward Sisler music experiment, 1946 (Box 430)
    - Gibson, E.
      - PK summary, 1935 (Box 430)
      - Long-distance PDT, RDT, 1936 (Box 430)
      - Subjects summary, 1936-1937 (Box 430)
      - Miscellaneous Woodruff data, 1937-1938, (3 folders) (Box 430)
      - Miscellaneous Woodruff data, 1937-1938, (3 folders) (Box 431)
      - Gibson-Mühl LD experiment, 1938, (5 folders) (Box 431)
      - Precognition correspondence experiment, 1938, (2 folders) (Box 431)
      - Precognition correspondence experiment 1938 (Box 432)
      - Gibson miscellany, 1938-1939 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 432)
      - Barometer study, 1938-1940, (2 folders) (Box 432)
      - Precognition correspondence experiment, 1938-1940, (3 folders) (Box 432)
      - Correspondence PDT, 1939 (Box 433)
      - Watts Hospital ESP experiment, 1939 (Box 433)
      - Detroit DT, 1941 (Box 433)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box 433)
      - Salience study rejects, 1941 (Box 433)
      - Doubles around the dice, 1942-1943, (2 folders) (Box 433)
      - Penny PK, 1943 (Box 433)
      - Dice studies, 1944 (Box 433)
      - Penny PK, 1944 (Box 433)
      - Around the dice, 1945 (Box 433)
      - Dry vs wet cage PK, 1945, (2 folders) (Box 433)
      - Miscellaneous analyses, undated, (7 folders) (Box 434)
      - Price “competition” experiment, undated (Box 434)
      - Exploratory PK, 1954 (Box 434)
    - Gillman, G.
      - Skidmore ESP trials, 1947, (12 folders) (Box 434)
      - Skidmore ESP trials, 1947, (6 folders) (Box 435)
      - Skidmore clairvoyance study, 1947-1948, (7 folders) (Box 435)
      - Skidmore clairvoyance study, 1947-1948 (Box 436)
    - Gordon, H. Pure telepathy, 1946 (Box 436)
    - Grant, M. Playing cards, 1952-1955, (3 folders) (Box 436)
    - Grassman, R. Training School study, 1938-1939 (Box 436)
    - Greenwood, J. Empirical check series, 1937 (Box 436)
    - Hallett, S.
      - Concentration technique, 1951 (Box 436)
      - Hazelgrove series, 1951 (Box 436)
      - Precognition trials, 1951 (Box 436)
      - State School for the Blind, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 437)
      - Wright Refuge study, 1951, (4 folders) (Box 437)
      - State School for the Blind, 1951(3 notebooks) (Box 437)
    - Hart, H. Drawings, undated (Box 438)
    - Hess, R. ESP test, 1949, (4 folders) (Box 438)
    - Hornaday, J.
      - Conscious control of automatic activities, 1935, (4 folders) (Box 438)
      - WCUWC study, 1949 (Box 439)
      - Helen Bryson Study, 1955 (Box 439)
      - PK - Attitude, undated, (5 folders) (Box 439)
    - Humphrey, B.
      - Dice check data, 1936 (Box 439)
      - Drug trials, 1936-1937 (Box 439)
      - Woodruff-Stuart machine PDT, 1937-1938, (2 folders) (Box 439)
      - Woodruff-Stuart machine PDT, 1937-1938, (3 folders) (Box 440)
      - Earlham College IQ series [1938] (Box 440)
      - Woodruff PDT, 1939-1941, (3 folders) (Box 440)
      - Hutchinson PDT, 1940, (4 folders) (Box 440)
      - Odds and ends, 1940 (Box 440)
      - GESP trials, 1940-1941, (10 folders) (Box 441)
      - Distance GESP, 1941 (Box 441)
      - General Salience survey, 1941? (Box 441)
      - Immediate vs. delayed check, 1941, (5 folders) (Box 441)
      - Immediate vs. delayed check, 1941, (11 folders) (Box 442)
      - Immediate vs. delayed check, 1941, (5 folders) (Box 443)
      - Individual subjects' performance, 1941, (3 folders) (Box 443)
      - Sophisticated subjects, 1941 (Box 443)
      - Rhine-Humphrey: Salience ratios, 1941, (9 folders) (Box 443)
      - Rhine-Humphrey: Salience ratios, 1941, (6 folders) (Box 444)
      - Salience ratios in Gibson correspondence experiment, 1941? (Box 444)
      - Rhine-Humphrey: terminal salience, 1941, (8 folders) (Box 444)
      - Rhine-Humphrey terminal salience, 1941, (10 folders) (Box 445)
      - Rhine-Humphrey transoceanic ESP, 1941? (Box 445)
      - Stuart PDT and DT-X analyses, 1941? (Box 445)
      - Brinson PK dice vs. cards, 1942 (Box 445)
      - ESP trials, 1942 (Box 445)
      - Free thowing, 1940 (Box 445)
      - Misc. dice tests, 1942 (Box 445)
      - Rhine-Humphrey: PK and precognition, 1942, (2 folders) (Box 445)
      - PK self-record, 1942 (Box 446)
      - “No. 10 Miscellaneous,” 1942and undated (Box 446)
      - Rhine-Humphrey: PK and precognition, 1942, (8 folders) (Box 446)
      - Hard-easy PK, 1942-1943 (Box 446)
      - Drawing experiment, 1943, (2 folders) (Box 446)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1944 (Box 446)
      - Gibson penny PK analysis, 1944? (Box 446)
      - Schwartz 2-dice data, 1944 (Box 446)
      - Interests and ESP, 1944-1945, (3 folders) (Box 447)
      - McMahan-Humphrey shock experiment, 1945 (Box 447)
      - McMahan-Humphrey unknown target series, 1945 (Box 447)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948 (Box 447)
      - Duke Dames group experiment, 1946 (Box 447)
      - Gibson GESP and clairvoyance, 1946, (2 folders) (Box 447)
      - McHahon ESP trials, 1946 (Box 447)
      - Miscellaneous runs and drawings, 1947-1948 (Box 447)
      - Handbook of Tests, 1947-1948, (5 folders) (Box 448)
      - Dice tests, 1948 (Box 448)
      - Pope Hill DT clairvoyance, 1948 (Box 448)
      - “Repetition” Stuart T-Test experiment, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 449)
      - Scriven Australian experiment, 1948 (Box 449)
      - 10 Year Symposium Digest, 1948 (Box 449)
      - Humphrey-McMahan exploratory dice tests, 1948-1949? (Box 449)
      - Lafgren clairvoyance drawing experiment, 1948-1949 (Box 449)
      - Self-testing club tests, 1948-1949 (Box 449)
      - Unknown series, 1948-1949? (Box 449)
      - Interests and ESP, 1949, (10 folders) (Box 450)
      - Raleigh experiment, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 450)
      - Raleigh experiment, 1950, (4 folders) (Box 451)
      - Sheep-goat and interests, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 451)
      - Card series prediction formula, undated (Box 451)
      - Changes of call, undated, (2 folders) (Box 451)
      - Cross-reference cards, undated (Box 452)
      - ESP runs, undated, (8 folders) (Box 452)
      - GESP drawings, undated (Box 452)
      - High school GESP, undated, (2 folders) (Box 452)
      - Item analyses, undated (Box 452)
      - Louisville drawing time experiment, undated, (4 folders) (Box 452)
      - Martin and Stribic analyses, undated (Box 452)
    - Kahn, S. Mechanical scoring technique, 1949-1950 (Box 452)
    - Kapchan, J.
      - ESP by clinical category, 1949 (Box 452)
      - Dramatic group tests, undated (Box 452)
      - Dramatic group tests, undated, (4 folders) (Box 453)
      - Non-dramatic group, undated (Box 453)
      - Dramatic group tests, undated (Box 453)
    - Kaplan, S. Tests with A. J., 1940-1950, (2 folders) (Box 453)
    - Killick, G. Two-dice psychokinesis, 1949, (2 folders) (Box 454)
    - Krause, Psychokinesis trials, undated (Box 454)
    - Krieger, E.
      - Psychokinesis self-tests, 1943 (Box 454)
      - Psychokinesis ESP self-tests, 1943-1944 (Box 454)
    - Kunkle, R. Elipeptics DT, 1951 (Box 454)
    - Landon, G. J.J. color experiment, 1955 (Box 454)
    - Lawrence, A.
      - Single card calling, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 454)
      - ESP and personality, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 454)
      - ESP and personality, 1948-1949, (19 folders) (Box 455)
    - McConnell, R. Clairvoyance self-tests, 1947 (Box 456)
    - MacFarland, J. Machine-shuffle precognition, 1938-1939, (4 folders) (Box 456)
    - McMahan, E.
      - Staff personality inventories, 1938, 1939, 1951 (Box 456)
      - PDT trials, 1940 (Box 456)
      - ESP marbles, 1941 (Box 456)
      - A.S.T.C. tests, 1943, (2 folders) (Box 456)
      - Family correspondence, 1943-1954 (Box 456)
      - Family correspondence, 1943-1954, (3 folders) (Box 457)
      - ESP-psychokinesis experiment, 1944 (Box 457)
      - (McMahan-Humphrey) PK tests, 1944 (Box 457)
      - PK discs, 1944-1945, (8 folders) (Box 457)
      - Psychokinesis (PK) discs, 1944-1945 (Box 458)
      - Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 458)
      - Series TI, 1945, (2 folders) (Box 458)
      - PT and clairvoyance, 1945-1946, (9 folders) (Box 458)
      - GESP trials, 1946 (Box 458)
      - PT-precognition - PK, 1946-1947 (Box 459)
      - Precognition summary, 1946-1951 (Box 459)
      - Drug PK series, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 459)
      - Dr. Rhine's discussion group, 1949 (Box 459)
      - Fitz-Gerald handwriting experiment, 1947? (Box 459)
      - Jennie Cox drawings, 1947 (Box 459)
      - Fleming precognition experiment, 1947, (6 folders) (Box 459)
      - Fleming precognition experiment, 1947, (3 folders) (Box 460)
      - Lauer, Joan: “Hide-and-seek” experiment, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 460)
      - Precognition experiment vs. PT, 1947 (Box 460)
      - Sanderson drawings, 1947 (Box 460)
      - Guilford College experiment, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 460)
      - Guilford College experiment, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 461)
      - Pope Hill precognition drawings, 1948 (Box 461)
      - Record sheets, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 461)
      - Mrs. Rush Temp and OM, 1948 (Box 461)
      - Morris Skibinsky tests, 1948 (Box 461)
      - Toksvig distance ESP, 1948 (Box 461)
      - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 461)
      - Handwriting experiment, 1948-1949 (Box 461)
      - Kamerer distance PDT, 1948-1950 (Box 461)
      - Marble boards, 1948-1949, (3 folders) (Box 462)
      - Charles Ozanne correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 462)
      - Correspondence w/ Vlad Sturdza, 1948-1952 (Box 462)
      - Greene and Andrews trials, 1949 (Box 462)
      - Killick PK trials, 1949 (Box 462)
      - Myrl McMahan self-tests, 1949, (2 folders) (Box 462)
      - Precognition trials, 1949 (Box 462)
      - Preliminary PK vs. precognition, 1949 (Box 463)
      - Shackleton photo experiment, 1949 (Box 463)
      - STM-precognition, 1949, (5 folders) (Box 463)
      - 1-yr. precog. vs. clairvoyance, 1949-1950 (Box 463)
      - Visitor's folder, 1949-1951, (2 folders) (Box 463)
      - Self-testing club, 1949-1952, (9 folders) (Box 464)
      - Self-testing club, 1949-1952, (7 folders) (Box 465)
      - Self-testing club, 1949-1952, (9 folders) (Box 466)
      - Self-testing club, 1949-1952, (7 folders) (Box 467)
      - Self-testing club, 1949-1952, (6 folders) (Box 468)
      - Clairvoyance and precognition, 1950 (Box 469)
      - Correspondence while in Europe, 1950, (2 folders) (Box 469)
      - Duke DT and 1 yr. precog., 1950, (2 folders) (Box 469)
      - Lossin, E. J.: Hypnosis precog., 1950 (Box 469)
      - Lossin hypnosis precognition, 1950 (Box 469)
      - McMahan-Humphrey: PK w/ children, 1950 (Box 469)
      - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 469)
      - Important correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 470)
      - Parapsychology correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 470)
      - BT-STM-Personality, 1951 (Box 470)
      - Cambridge-Duke ESP, 1951 (Box 470)
      - PK and clairvoyance, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 470)
      - Prediction of baby's sex, 1951 (Box 470)
      - PSI clinic, 1951 (Box 470)
      - Exploration trial, 1951-1953 (Box 471)
      - DT and precognition, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Double-aspect experiment, 1952? (Box 471)
      - Election prediction, 1952 (Box 471)
      - ESP with foreign students, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Hypnotic suggestion, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Lemuel Blades tests, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Method for determining precognition target sequences, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Normal vs. timed STM, 1952 (Box 471)
      - North Carolina College series, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Predicting Democratic nominees, 1952 (Box 471)
      - Psi-missing experiment, 1952, (3 folders) (Box 471)
      - Taylor machine trials, 1952 (Box 472)
      - 3-dice tests, 1952 (Box 472)
      - Triple aspect ESP, 1952 (Box 472)
      - Dual-target precognition, 1952-1953 (Box 472)
      - Clairvoyance and precognition, 1953 (Box 472)
      - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 472)
      - Correspondence with W. P. Bentley, 1953 (Box 472)
      - Immediate precognition, 1953 (Box 472)
      - McMahan-Rhine, S.L.: Variation of technique test for visitors' target sheets, 1953 (Box 472)
      - 100 precognition runs, 1953 (Box 472)
      - Clairvoyance trials, 1953-1954 (Box 472)
      - Opik precognition experiment, 1953-1954 (Box 472)
      - Opik precognition experiment, 1953-1954 (Box 473)
      - Correspondence, 1954, (2 folders) (Box 473)
      - Osis divided target LD experiment, 1954 (Box 473)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, undated (Box 473)
      - Interest tests, undated (Box 473)
      - PT experiment 6, undated (Box 473)
      - Rush drawings, undated (Box 473)
      - Cross Reference Cards (Box 473)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 473)
      - “Odds and ends of items” (Box 473)
      - GESP runs, 1940 (Box 473)
      - Exploratory PK tests, 1934-1936 (Box 473)
      - “Blind” PK, 1943 (Box 473)
    - Millet, M. Precognition tests with children, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 474)
    - Metcalf, J. Metcalf-McMahan: Distance GESP, 1947-1948, (2 folders) (Box 474)
    - Newton, M. Chautauqa children experiment, 1951 (Box 474)
    - Nielsen, W.
      - GESP testing, 1954 (Box 474)
      - Miscellaneous records, 1954-1956 (Box 474)
      - Miscellaneous testing, 1954-1955 (Box 474)
      - Precog. experiment, 1954-1955, (4 folders) (Box 474)
      - Precog. trials, 1954-1956, (10 folders) (Box 475)
      - Self-tests, 1954-1955 (Box 475)
      - Clairvoyance-mood experiment, 1955 (Box 475)
      - Correspondence w/ Mrs. Chester Bellows, 1955 (Box 475)
      - First mood experiment, 1955, (3 folders) (Box 475)
      - Precog. run distribution, 1955, (3 folders) (Box 475)
      - Precog. run distribution, 1955, (7 folders) (Box 476)
      - Personality and mood tests, 1955, (4 folders) (Box 476)
      - Precog. vs. clairvoyance, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 476)
      - Precognitive PK, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 476)
      - Random number table matching, 1955 (Box 476)
      - Jeanne Shearer experiment, 1955 (Box 477)
      - Si Weiss precognition experiment, 1955 (Box 477)
      - Study of Values experiment, 1955 (Box 477)
      - Correspondence, 1955-1956, (3 folders) (Box 477)
      - Correspondence with Nan Gerding, 1955-1956 (Box 477)
      - GESP trials, 1955-1956, (4 folders) (Box 477)
      - Home experimenters, 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 477)
      - Home experimenters, 1955-1956, (8 folders) (Box 478)
      - Long-range precognition, 1955-1956 (Box 478)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1955-1956 (Box 478)
      - Student's sheep-goat experiment, 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 478)
      - Cormack targets, 1956 (Box 478)
      - Experiment for Banham, 1956 (Box 478)
      - Gerding-Neilsen distance experiments, 1956, (2 folders) (Box 478)
      - Gerding-Nielsen distance experiment, 1956 (Box 479)
      - Mood scale III, 1956 (Box 479)
      - Sense out of nonsense tests, 1956 (Box 479)
      - Freeman precog. test, 1961, (2 folders) (Box 479)
      - Freeman mother-child experiment, 1963 (Box 479)
      - Precognition test, 1963 (Box 479)
      - Stewart-Klopper lab correspondence, 1963 (Box 479)
      - MWC ESP experiments, 1963, (6 folders) (Box 479)
      - Otani ESP summary, 1963 (Box 480)
      - ESP and emotional variables, 1964, (9 folders) (Box 480)
      - ESP masks, 1964 (Box 480)
      - Precognition experiment, 1964 (Box 480)
      - Guess Which One?, 1965 (Box 480)
      - Guess Which One?, 1965 (Box 481)
      - Martin Johnson classroom ESP, 1970 (Box 481)
      - Shipley experiment, 1970 (Box 481)
      - Ware paper, 1970 (Box 481)
      - Cohen precognition study, 1970-1971 (Box 481)
      - Duplessis collective test, 1970-1971 (Box 481)
      - Bibliography for physiological correlates, undated (Box 481)
      - Freeman data, undated (Box 481)
      - Humm-Wadsworth Temperament Scale, undated (Box 481)
      - Ascendence-Submission Personality Inventory, undated (Box 481)
      - Bernreuter Personality Inventory, undated (Box 481)
      - Miscellaneous blanks, undated (Box 481)
      - Mood analyses, undated (Box 481)
    - Osis, K.
      - Alphabetical files, 1950-1956, (9 folders) (Box 481)
      - Alphabetical files, 1950-1956(14 files) (Box 482)
      - Alphabetical files, 1950-1956, (19 folders) (Box 483)
      - Correspondence with H.A. Koegel, 1951-1952 (Box 483)
      - ESP-PK experiment, 1952, (4 folders) (Box 483)
      - Exploratory cat experiment 1952, (10 folders) (Box 484)
      - First cat experiment, 1952, (20 folders) (Box 484)
      - First cat experiment, 1952, (16 folders) (Box 485)
      - Häckel LD experiment, 1953, (3 folders) (Box 485)
      - Second cat experiment, 1953, (11 folders) (Box 485)
      - Second cat experiment, 1953, (7 folders) (Box 486)
      - Correspondence with B. Sokoloff, 1953-1954 (Box 486)
      - Work with Olof Jonsson, 1954, (6 folders) (Box 486)
      - Correspondence with G. Junger, 1954-1955 (Box 486)
      - Correspondence tests, 1954-1956, (2 folders) (Box 486)
      - Correspondence tests, 1954-1956, (15 folders) (Box 487)
      - Correspondence tests, 1954-1956, (18 folders) (Box 488)
      - Correspondence tests, 1954-1956, (10 folders) (Box 489)
      - Loughborough precog. experiment, 1954-1955, (2 folders) (Box 489)
      - Correspondence with R. Tonndorf, 1955-1956 (Box 489)
      - Ehrenburg ESP record sheets, 1956 (Box 489)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1956 (Box 489)
      - Osis-Pienaar, D.C.: Long-distance experiment, 1956 (Box 489)
      - Osis-Piennar: Long distance experiment, 1956 (Box 489)
      - Work with Susy Smith, 1956, (2 folders) (Box 489)
      - Diary of experiments, undated (Box 489)
      - Longman Sittings, undated (Box 489)
    - Oswald, I. (Box 490)
      - PK for precognized targets, 1950 (Box 490)
      - Latin Square experiment, 1951 (Box 490)
      - Short series, 1951 (Box 490)
      - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 490)
    - Pope, D.
      - Caffeine PK, 1942 (Box 490)
      - Psychokinesis tests, 1942-1943 (Box 490)
      - ESP data, 1945, (2 folders) (Box 490)
      - Psychokinesis data, 1948 (Box 490)
    - Pratt, J.G.
      - Rat learning studies, c. 1932-1936, (3 folders) (Box 490)
      - Rat learning studies, c. 1932-1936, (3 folders) (Box 491)
      - Pearce-Pratt distance series, 1933 (Box 491)
      - Garrett miscellaneous ESP, 1934 (Box 491)
      - Garrett PDT (C34,5), 1934 (Box 491)
      - Garrett study background data, 1934 (Box 491)
      - Carpenter and Phalan data (D-61), 1935, (3 folders) (Box 491)
      - Early New York work, 1935 (Box 492)
      - Woodruff ESP data, 1935 (Box 492)
      - Bamman experiments, 1935-1936, (2 folders) (Box 492)
      - Lottie Bigson ESP trials, 1935-1936, (2 folders) (Box 492)
      - Misc. New York data, 1935-1936, (5 folders) (Box 492)
      - New York with Eileen Garrett, 1935-1936 (Box 493)
      - C. Hilton Rice study, 1936-1937, (7 folders) (Box 493)
      - Work with Mrs. Manter, 1935-1937 (Box 493)
      - Work with Mrs. Manter, 1935-1937, (7 folders) (Box 494)
      - Work with Mrs. Manter, 1935-1937, (2 folders) (Box 495)
      - Carpenter work with Daniel Lopez, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Kerr-Pratt series, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Laboratory ledger, 1936 (Box 495)
      - McFarland aesthetic-unaesthetic study, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Union Group experiment, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Welsh hypnosis experiment, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Work with D. L. Evans, 1936 (Box 495)
      - Estabrooks experiment, 1937 (Box 496)
      - Gibson PK, 1936-1939, (3 folders) (Box 496)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1936-1937 (Box 496)
      - Work with J. J. Dowd, 1936-1937 (Box 496)
      - New York ESP trials, 1937, (45 folders) (Box 496)
      - New York Misc. data, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 497)
      - P = 1/25 experiment, 1937 (Box 497)
      - Woodruff Des Moines PDT, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 497)
      - Work with Gladys Huss, 1937 (Box 497)
      - Summarized ESP data, 1937-1938, (5 folders) (Box 497)
      - Summarized ESP data, 1937-1938, (5 folders) (Box 498)
      - University of Colorado data, 1937-1939, (7 folders) (Box 498)
      - Instructions on ESP techniques, c. 1938 (Box 498)
      - McFarland 2-agent GESP, 1938 (Box 499)
      - Pratt-Woodruff series, 1938, (4 folders) (Box 499)
      - Rat experiment, 1938 (Box 499)
      - STM screen drawing, 1938 (Box 499)
      - Zenith Radio report, 1938 (Box 499)
      - Newman data, 1939 (Box 499)
      - Pratt-Woodruff cross-check, 1939 (Box 499)
      - Pratt-Woodruff scores, 1939, (5 folders) (Box 500)
      - Pratt-Woodruff scores, 1939, (4 folders) (Box 501)
      - Herbert Dixon ESP trials, 1939 (Box 501)
      - Stuart-Pratt tempo study, 1939 (Box 501)
      - Vocational interest blanks, 1939 (Box 501)
      - Bernreuter Personality Inventories, 1940 (Box 501)
      - Carington materials, 1940 (Box 501)
      - Hutchinson precognition summary, 1940 (Box 501)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1940 (Box 501)
      - 3/5 and 53 preliminary testing, 1940 (Box 501)
      - Pratt-Woodward PK summaries, 1940 (Box 502)
      - Pratt-Woodruff precog. experiment, 1940 (Box 502)
      - Rotating-cage PK experiment, 1940 (Box 502)
      - Roll box, c. 1940 (Box 502)
      - Graduate Research Council, 1940-1941 (Box 502)
      - Woodruff Sensory Deception date, 1940-1941, (3 folders) (Box 502)
      - Codes, 1940-1941, (2 folders) (Box 502)
      - ESP marbles, 1941 (Box 502)
      - ESP marbles, 1941 (Box 503)
      - Humphrey-Pratt College GESP, 1941, (2 folders) (Box 503)